OUR PODCAST
IS THE
GROWTH GARDEN
BY CARROT.
IT IS
A PODCAST
FOR ANYBODY
WHO IS
A MARKETER
A BUSINESS
OWNER
OR A
SALES LEADER
WHO IS
TRYING TO
GROW IN
THIS NEW
WORLD OF
AI SEARCH.
THE VU
STUDIO IS
ONE OF
MY FAVORITE
PARTS OF
WORKING AT
THIS INCUBATOR.
SO SP-ARK
LABS HAS
SET IT
UP SO
THAT WE
HAVE A
BEAUTIFUL BACKGROUND
FOR JUST
REGULAR PRODUCT
VIDEOS IN
THE CORNER.
WE HAVE
A GREAT
PODCAST STUDIO
AND MULTIPLE
ROOMS THERE.
BUT MOST
IMPORTANTLY
WE HAVE
THIS INCREDIBLE
SCREEN BEHIND
US THAT
ALLOWS YOU
TO DO
ALL KINDS
OF INTERACTIVE
VIDEOS
PRODUCT DEMOS
AND MAKE
IT LOOK
LIKE YOU
ARE MUCH
BIGGER THAN
YOU ARE
IN THE
EARLY DAYS
WHICH IS
VERY HELPFUL
FOR FOUNDERS.
YEAH
COMING UP
ON THE
GROWTH GARDEN
WE ARE
DOING A
PREVIEW FOR
SEARCH SOUL
THE BIGGEST
SEO CONFERENCE
IN KOREA
COMING UP
IN SEPTEMBER.
WE HAVE
A FEW
SPEAKERS WHO
HAVE BEEN
UH
ALREADY RECORDED
AND DONE
THEIR EPISODES
AND WE
WILL BE
DROPPING CLIPS
OF THEM
AS PREVIEWS
SOON.
A SPECIAL
SHOUT-OUT TO
DANNY KIM
FOUNDER OF
ASCENT AI
AND NOW
UH
LOOKING MIND
WHICH IS
TOP SEO
AGENCY AND
AEO TOOL
IN KOREA.
WE APPRECIATE
HIM BEING
OUR FIRST
GUEST.